Jamie Joseph Heiney

Office Manager, AP AR, a wide range of tasks

About Me

I am a detail-oriented and skilled office manager with experience in managing accounts payable and accounts receivable, bank and credit card reconciliation, QuickBooks (Enterprise and Online), Google Sheets, Excel cash flow management, budgeting and financial planning, and excellent communication and simplify complex topics. I have a broad understanding of business and management, having developed interactive group games for elderly care facilities and managed accounts receivable, among other experiences. I am a graduate of Yeshiva Toras Chaim High School and have completed an accounting course by Harold Averkamp.

Skills

- Accounts Payable/Accounts Receivable (AP/AR)
- Bank & Credit Card Reconciliation
- QuickBooks (Enterprise and Online)
- Google Sheets
- Excel Cash Flow Management
- · Budgeting and Financial Planning
- Excellent communication
- Simplification of complex topics

Experience

Accountant

Dec 2019 - May 2022

- Served as an accountant for several capital funding companies, managing all their bookkeeping needs. Including creating chart of accounts, bank reconciliation. Organized, formatted, and imported large amounts of data from CRMS, other software and google sheets.
- Designed and implemented a comprehensive loan tracking system using multiple interlinked Google Sheets and Google App Scripts. The system allowed owners, salespeople, and outside investors to view and update vital information about current and former deals, with multiple permission levels and an intuitive UI.
- Utilized the accounting system for multiple companies owned by Alpha Capital and provided consulting services to other companies.

Nursing Home Game Creator

Feb 2017 - Feb 2019

- Developed interactive group games for elderly care facilities to address the lack of stimulating and engaging content for elders.
- Grew client base to over 30 nursing homes and hundreds of happy users.
- Managed accounts receivable and gained a broad understanding of business and management.

AP Regional Manager

Jan 2015 - Mar 2017

- Oversaw AP transactions and personnel for four nursing homes.
- Negotiated with vendors for more favorable contracts.
- Maintained all accounts payable reports, spreadsheets, and files.
- Acted as a liaison between corporate and nursing home accounts payable departments.
- Managed emails and website domains for the corporate staff.

Education

Certificate. Accounting Foundations Accounting Foundations: Bookkeeping QuickBooks

Online Essential Training QuickBooks Pro Essential Training

I completed a certificate in Accounting Foundations, including Bookkeeping and QuickBooks, as well as completed Essential Training for QuickBooks Pro through online courses. I also hold a diploma from Yeshiva Toras Chaim High School with a 3.4 GPA and completed an accounting course by Harold Averkamp.

Contact: 305-801-7497